hey today i want to help you with your
cartwheel and all you need is something
to
make a line
that's pretty good first off practice
your footwork stepping at an
angle to the line next up we're just
going to add in the hand work so with
one foot forward
the hands go on the line same side hand
leg opposite hand opposite leg
and then step back we'll put that in
motion so
one two three four gradually work on
kicking
the back leg one two three four
next up we'll start on the line but the
focus is only on the hand so the hands
go on the line
one two three four next up just try and
get one foot on the line
one two three four finally you can put
it all together one two three
four and that's how you can work on your
cartwheel